

ANDRIO PRATAMA SIRAIT

WEB, ANDROID AND IOS DEVELOPER

ONLINE PORTFOLIO

Visit

www.andriosirait.com

CONTACT

- +62 812 2669 6696
- Jl. Karya Bakti, Kota Pekanbaru, Prov. Riau
- in Andrio Pratama Sirait

ABOUT ME

A professional full-stack developer from Pekanbaru, Indonesia. 2 years experienced working on StartUp. Working for more than 10+ project. Im having big passion on business to give good impact for others, coding & technology to solve problem and streamline things with code. I always give my best for each projects I did. I give a solution with my creative app.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Co-founder & CTO WarungSegar

WarungSegar is a StartUp based on Pekanbaru, Riau that focus to cut food products supply chain. we make fresh products, easy to get for you, directly from farmers.

Oct 2019 until now

Co-founder Nginvite.com

Nginvite is StartUp based on Pekanbaru, Nginvite is an online invitation based on web application with self-service concept which allow user to create and choose design for their invitation. Nginvite have some invitation type such as wedding, meeting, informal and formal events

Oct 2021 until now

Fullstack Developer - SiteMedia

SiteMedia is a software house, accepts outsourcing of website, android and iOS application development. I work for some project on SiteMedia as fullstack developer

April 2021 until now

UNRI Software Engineering Assistant Laboratory

I was entrusted as Assistant Laboratory of Software Engineering on Riau University by Salhazan Nasution, S.Kom., MIT. I supervise student practicums and also check the results of the exercises.

August 2019 until April 2020



SKILL

LIBRARY/FRAMEWORK CORE **TOOLS** React Native GitHub Javascript React.js Next.js BitBucket PHP Codelaniter Laravel **iQuery** VS Code **Figma** Express

Express.is

EDUCATION

2016 - 2022

BACHELOR DEGREE / RIAU UNIVERSITY

Bachelor Degree of Informatics Engineering Department from Riau University. Graduated with 3.71 GPA.

SCSS

2013 - 2016

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL / SMA PLUS TARUNA ANDALAN

Bootstrap

Science major. Continue my interest into computer, won some blog design competition on provincial level. Also, start to learn a programming language with Pascal

Achievements:

- 2nd Winner (2014), Blogspot design competition by Public High School Plus Pekanbaru (provincial level competition)

 Event name: Fantasi10
- 3rd Winner (2014), Blogspot design competition by Telkom Pekanbaru and Pekanbaru Mall, Theme : Elevation (provincial level competition)

 Event name : Elevation

2010 - 2013

JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL / SMP GLOBAL ANDALAN

Started liked in computer, tried graphic design. Made a lot of projects in graphic design and video editing